{"data":[{"question":"Who _____ (move) the furniture about upstairs?","a":"are moving","b":"is moving","c":"is moveing","answer":"2","explain":"- Affirmative: he\/she\/it + is.\n- Move -> moving.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Question2","a":"A","b":"B ","c":"C ","answer":"are\/doing","explain":"3","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Question2","a":"A","b":"B ","c":"C ","answer":"are\/doing","explain":"3","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"What _____(make) that terrible noise?","a":"am making","b":"are making","c":"is making","answer":"3","explain":"- What + is + V-ing...?\n- Make -> making.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"I _____ (come) in a minute.","a":"is coming","b":"are coming","c":"am coming","answer":"3","explain":"- I + am + V-ing.\n- Come -> coming.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"I _____ (read) a book.","a":"are reading","b":"am reading","c":"is reading","answer":"2","explain":"- I + am + V-ing\n- Read -> reading","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"He _____ (teach) his boy to ride.","a":"am teaching","b":"is teaching","c":"are teaching","answer":"2","explain":"- He + is + V-ing.\n-Teach -> teaching.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"I _____ (wait) for my change.","a":"is waiting","b":"am waiting","c":"are waiting","answer":"2","explain":"- I + am +V-ing.\n- Wait -> waiting.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"It is a lovely day. The sun _____ (shine) and the birds _____ (sing).","a":"is shining\/is singing","b":"is shining\/are singing","c":"is shineing\/is singing","d":"are shining\/is singing","answer":"2","explain":"- The sun(singular) + is + V-ing.\n- The birds (plural) + are + V-ing.\n- Shine -> shining.\n- Sing -> singing.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They _____ (look) for oil.","a":"are looking","b":"is looking","c":"am looking","answer":"1","explain":"- They + are + V-ing.\n- Look -> looking.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"You _____ (not tell) the truth.","a":"aren't telling","b":"isn't telling","c":"am not telling","answer":"1","explain":"- You + are not\/aren't + V-ing.\n- Tell -> telling.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"}]}